PROFILE

Johns Hopkins University SAIS MA International Relations & Economics; University of Oxford BA in Japanese and Korean Studies. Past 5 years worked in Japan, Korea, Switzerland, Belgium, UK, USA: extensive public-sector experience and internships at Asian multinationals – swiftly adapted and contributed to organisations' goals. Excellent writing and communication skills. Strong self-starter and keen team-player.

EDUCATION

Johns Hopkins University School of Advanced International Studies (SAIS) Master of Arts, International Relations & Economics

Washington, DC May 2013

- Cumulative GPA: 3.73 (final semester 3.83)
- Concentration: Korean Studies (recipient: U.S.-Korea Institute Fellowship)
- Teacher's Assistant for: International Trade Theory, Behavioural Economics, English Writing Centre

University of Oxford

Oxford, England

Bachelor of Arts (Honours), Japanese and Korean Studies

June 2009

- First Class Honours' Degree with a Distinction in Spoken Japanese
- Scholarships: Gibbs Prize in Oriental Studies; Japanese Ministry of Education Scholarship (2007-2008)

EXPERIENCE

Korean Air, Cargo Marketing Department **Intern**

Seoul, Republic of Korea May-July 2012

- Learnt about logistics and air freight industries, Korean corporate culture
- Conducted in-depth independent market research including benchmarking, analysis of trade statistics writing and presenting a comprehensive report in Korean to director-level management
- Result: initiated expansion of a major cargo product with low market-share and adoption of growth strategy (freight type and region) according to my recommendations

Mitsui & Co. Benelux **Research Assistant**

Brussels, Belgium March-May 2011

- Learnt about CSR, Japanese trading-conglomerate business model, multi-lingual research
- Conducted comprehensive research on EU green buildings regulations; identified new business partners
- Result: initiated green renovation of offices (to cut costs and as an example of products to expand business)

European Commission, Taxation and Customs Union Directorate-General Trainee, Asia Sector, International Coordination Unit

Brussels, Belgium

• Learnt about EU institutions; within first 2 weeks presented team's position on international negotiations at

October 2010 – February 2011

commission-wide meeting; prepared various internal documents contributing to policy decision-making

Kyotanabe City Hall

Kyoto, Japan August 2009 - July 2010

Coordinator for International Relations (CIR)

• Established the city's international awareness campaign as the first CIR in Kyotanabe (another was contracted as my successor) - initiated and led multiple cultural events with 5-30 participants

• Adapted and successfully contributed to Japanese-language-only office culture and rigid hierarchy

Foreign and Commonwealth Office **Undergraduate Intern, Protocol Directorate**

London, England **July-August 2007**

• Shadowed a civil servant in each department; helped prepare a climate-change conference for diplomatic VIPs

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Languages: English (native); Japanese, German (fluent); Korean (advanced); French, Dutch (elementary) Technical Skills: MS Excel, MS Word, MS PowerPoint (advanced); financial statement analysis *UK citizen, authorised to work in the United States.*